http://www.parliament.gov.sg/privacy-statement

About Us
Please click the links on the right to find out more on what Parliament is about.
MPs
Please click the links on the right to find out more on MP related information.
Parliamentary Business
Please click the links on the right to access the various Parliamentary Business items.
Official Reports (Parl Debates)
Glossary
Select Committee on Deliberate Online Falsehoods – Causes, Consequences and Countermeasures
Newsroom
Please click the links on the right to find out more about events happening at Parliament.
Speaker's Blog
Events
Press Releases
Visit & Learn
Please click the links on the right to learn more about visiting Parliament.
History
Please click the links on the right to learn more about the history of Parliament.
Proclamation of Independence
I am a ...
I am a Visitor
I wish to ...
Know more about Parliament
Book a tour
Visit Parliament House
I am a Researcher
I wish to ...
Privacy Statement
This is a Government of Singapore digital service.
We may use "cookies", where a small data file is sent to your browser to store and track information about you when you enter our digital service. The cookie is used to track information such as the number of users and their frequency of use, profiles of users and their preferred digital services. While this cookie can tell us when you enter our digital services and which pages you visit, it cannot read data off your hard disk.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the digital service.
If you provide us with personally identifiable data
a)     Where appropriate, we may share necessary data with other Government agencies, so as to improve the discharge of public functions, and to serve you in the most efficient and effective way unless such sharing is prohibited by law.
b)     We will NOT share your Personal Data with non-Government entities, except where such entities have been authorised to carry out specific Government services.
c)     For your convenience, we may also display to you data you had previously supplied us or other Government Agencies.  This will speed up the transaction and save you the trouble of repeating previous submissions. Should the data be out-of-date, please supply us the latest data.
To safeguard your personal data, all electronic storage and transmission of personal data are secured with appropriate security technologies.
This digital service may contain links to non-Government digital services whose data protection and privacy practices may differ from ours. We are not responsible for the content and privacy practices of these other websites and encourage you to consult the privacy notices of those sites.
Please contact Parliament’s QSM at parl_cop@parl.gov.sg if you:
a)     have any enquires or feedback on our data protection policies and procedures,
b)     need more information on or access to data which you have provided to us in the past.
©2017 Singapore Parliament. All Rights Reserved.
This website is optimised for Chrome 68, 67, Safari 11, 10, Internet Explorer 11, 10, Firefox 61, 60 and Microsoft Edge 42, 41.
Last Updated 07/06/2019
